Guide to the Vassar College Facilities Operations Records, 1800s-2021 (bulk 1908-1999)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series II. Plans, 1800s - 2010
  - Frances Lehman Loeb Art Center, 1990-1992
    - [Plans] Loeb Art Center, undated (Map Case - Drawer 106)
  - Main Building, 1891-1989
    - [Plans] Main Building - Drawings, 1891, 1970; (2 items) (Map Case - Drawer 60)
    - [Plans] Main Building, 1893; (1 item) (Map Case - Drawer 52)
    - [Plans] Main Building - Library - Proposed Plans, 1893, 1917; (7 items) (Map Case - Drawer 60)
    - [Plans] Main Building - Architectural Drawings (Folder 1 of 3), 1905, 1936, undated; (12 items) (Map Case - Drawer 60)
    - [Plans] Main Building, circa 1906-1907 (Roll Boxes 147-148)
    - [Plans] Main Building East Wing, 1907 (Roll Box 146)
    - [Plans] Main Building Basement Heating and Lighting, 1910 (Roll Box 160)
    - [Plans] "Main Building", 1913 (Roll Box 160)
    - [Plans] Alterations to Main Building, 1918 (Roll Box 153)
    - [Plans] Alterations to Main Building, Allen and Collens, 1918 (Roll Box 154)
    - [Plans] Alterations to Main Building, Allen and Collens, 1918 (Roll Box 158)
    - [Plans] Main Building, 1926; (1 item) (Map Case - Drawer 52)
    - [Plans] Main Building Basement Ash Hopper, 1933-1934 (Roll Box 151)
    - [Plans] Main Building "DC to AC Conversion", 1936 (Roll Box 247)
    - [Plans] Main Building North Corridor, 1937 (Roll Box 170)
    - [Plans] Main Building Space Analysis of a Typical Dormitory Floor, Eero Saarinen, 1955 (Roll Box 156)
    - [Plans] Alterations to Main Building, 1959 (Roll Box 149)
    - [Plans] Alterations to Main Building, 1959 (Roll Box 157)
    - [Plans] Main Building - Alterations, architectural paintings, 1960; (2 items) (Map Case - Drawer 46)
    - [Plans] Main Building, 1960 (Roll Box 155)
    - [Plans] Main Building, [1960]; (1 item) (Map Case - Drawer 52)
    - [Plans] Main Building Floor Plan, 1965 (Roll Box 277)
    - [Plans] Main Building (revised 1973), 1965, 1973 (Roll Box 254)
    - [Plans] Main Building, 1968 (Roll Box 153)
    - [Plans] Main Building, 1968 (Roll Box 156)
    - [Plans] Main Building, 1969 (Roll Box 217)
    - [Plans] Main Building Sprinkler System Plan, 1970 (Roll Box 218)
    - [Plans] College Center, 1971 (Roll Box 260)
    - [Plans] Main Building College Center, 1972 (Roll Box 82)
    - [Plans] Main Building- College Center, 1973 (Roll Box 40)
    - [Plans] College Center, 1973 (Roll Box 217)
    - [Plans] College Center, Shepley, Bowfinch, Richardson, and Abbott, 1973 (Roll Box 237)
    - [Plans] College Center, 1973 (Roll Box 240)
    - [Plans] Utility Plan for College Center "Bid Drawings Not Built," Shepley, Bulfinch, Richardson, and Abbott, 1973 (Roll Box 248)
    - [Plans] College Center, 1973 (Roll Box 251)
    - [Plans] College Center, Shepley, Bulfinch, Richardson, and Abbott, 1973 (Roll Box 251)
    - [Plans] College Center, Shepley, Bulfinch, Richardson, Abbott, 1973 (Roll Box 253)
    - [Plans] College Center, Shepley, Bulfinch, etc., 1973 (Roll Box 256)
    - [Plans] College Center, 1973 (Roll Box 257)
    - [Plans] Vassar College Center Utility Plan, 1973 (Roll Box 258)
    - [Plans] College Center, 1973 (Roll Box 274)
    - [Plans] College Center, 1973 (Roll Box 294)
    - [Plans] Main Building Office Rehab. Second Floor, 1986 (Roll Box 159)
    - [Plans] Main Building, revised, 1989 (Roll Box 156)
    - [Plans] "Original Drawings: Second Floor Main Building" Hutchins, Evans & Lefferts, undated (Roll Box 36)
    - [Plans] Alterations to Main Building, Allen and Collens, undated (Roll Box 151)
    - [Plans] Fragment of Main Building, undated (Roll Box 152)
    - [Plans] Main Building, undated (Map Case - Drawer 107)
    - [Plans] Main Building, undated (Map Case - Drawer 108)
    - [Plans] Main Building, undated (Roll Box 336)
    - [Plans] Main Building, undated (Roll Box 337)
    - [Plans] Main Building, undated (Roll Box 338)
    - [Plans] Main Building - Architectural Drawings (Folder 2 of 3), undated; (5 items) (Map Case - Drawer 60)
    - [Plans] Main Building - Architectural Drawings (Folder 3 of 3), undated; (6 items) (Map Case - Drawer 60)
    - [Plans] Main Building ?, undated (Roll Box 218)
    - [Plans] Main Building Alterations after 1918 Fire, undated (Roll Box 152)
    - [Plans] Main Building HVAC, undated (Roll Box 159)
    - [Plans] Main Building Miscellaneous, undated (Roll Box 293)
    - [Plans] Planned Alterations to Main Building, Allen and Collens, undated (Roll Box 145)
  - Metcalf House, 1915, 1970
    - [Plans] Metcalf, 1915 (Roll Box 153)
    - [Plans] Metcalf, 1915 (Roll Box 161)
    - [Plans] Metcalf, 1970 (Roll Box 215)
    - [Plans] Metcalf House, undated (Map Case - Drawer 111)
  - Seeley G. Mudd Chemistry Building, 1981-1989
    - [Plans] Mudd Chemistry Original Design by Dubin Bloone - "Not Built", 1981 (Roll Box 238)
    - [Plans] Mudd Chemistry, 1982 (Roll Box 40)
    - [Plans] Mudd Chemistry, 1982 (Roll Box 323)
    - [Plans] Mudd Chemistry, 1982-1983 (Roll Boxes 20-24)
    - [Plans] "Mudd not as built", 1983 (Roll Box 19)
    - [Plans] Mudd Chemistry - "Hope’s Windows", 1983 (Roll Box 25)
    - [Plans] Mudd Chemistry, 1987 (Roll Box 32)
    - [Plans] Mudd Chemistry, 1989 (Roll Box 18)
    - [Plans] Mudd Chemistry, undated (Map Case - Drawer 112)
    - [Plans] Seeley Mudd Chemistry Building - Miscellaneous HVAC Plans, undated (Roll Box 239)
  - New England Building, 1900-1990
    - [Plans] New England, 1900 (Roll Box 106)
    - [Plans] New England Building Lighting, Timmis, 1910 (Roll Box 172)
    - [Plans] New England Building, 1966 (Roll Box 214)
    - [Plans] New England Building Alterations, 1990 (Roll Box 165)
    - [Plans] "Original Drawings: New England Basement" Hutchins, Evans and Lefferts, undated (Roll Box 36)
    - [Plans] New England Building, undated (Map Case - Drawer 113)
    - [Plans] New England Building, undated (Roll Box 171)
  - New Hackensack Building, undated
    - [Plans] New Hackensack Building, undated (Map Case - Drawer 114)
  - Observatory - Class of 1951, undated
    - [Plans] Class of 1951 Observatory, undated (Map Case - Drawer 116)
  - Observatory - Maria Mitchell, [1895]
    - [Plans] Observatory - Specifications for addition, [1895]; (2 copies) (Map Case - Drawer 57)
    - [Plans] Maria Mitchell Observatory, undated (Map Case - Drawer 116)
    - [Plans] Maria Mitchell Observatory, undated (Roll Box 320)
  - Old Laundry Building (Computer Center), 1964-1986
    - [Plans] Old Laundry Building, 1966 (Roll Box 106)
  - Olmsted Hall of Biological Sciences, 1969-1973
    - [Plans] Olmsted Hall plans, 1969 (Roll Box 350)
    - [Plans] Olmsted Hall plans, 1969 (Roll Box 351)
    - [Plans] Biological Sciences Building Utilities, 1969-1970 (Roll Box 232)
    - [Plans] Olmsted Hall plans, 1970 (Roll Box 352)
    - [Plans] Olmsted Hall plans, 1970 (Roll Box 362)
    - [Plans] "Biological Sciences Building", 1971 (Roll Boxes 26-28)
    - [Plans] Biological Sciences Building HVAC Plans, 1971 (Roll Box 236)
    - [Plans] Biological Sciences Building, 1971 (Roll Boxes 250-251)
    - [Plans] Biological Sciences Building Mechanicals, 1971 (Roll Box 252)
    - [Plans] Biological Sciences Building Fire Doors, 1971 (Roll Box 263)
    - [Plans] Olmsted Hall plans, 1971 (Roll Box 353)
    - [Plans] Olmsted Hall plans, 1971 (Roll Box 354)
    - [Plans] Biological Sciences Building, 1971-1973 (Roll Boxes 233-234)
    - [Plans] Biological Sciences Building, 1971, 1973 (Roll Box 263)
    - [Plans] "Biological Sciences Building", 1972 (Roll Box 33)
    - [Plans] Architect’s Corrections - Biological Sciences Greenhouse, T. Engstrand, 1972 (Roll Box 232)
    - [Plans] Biological Sciences Building, 1972 (Roll Box 252)
    - [Plans] "Biological Sciences, IBG and Greenhouse", 1973 (Roll Box 37)
    - [Plans] Biological Sciences Building Skylights, 1973 (Roll Box 237)
    - [Plans] Olmsted Hall, undated; (1 item) (Map Case - Drawer 49)
    - [Plans] Olmsted, undated (Map Case - Drawer 117)
    - [Plans] Biological Sciences Building, undated (Roll Box 236)
  - Poughkeepsie Day School, 1963
    - [Plans] Poughkeepsie Day School, 1963 (Roll Boxes 319-320)
    - [Plans] Poughkeepsie Day School, 2500 New Hackensack, undated (Map Case - Drawer 119)
  - Hallie Flanagan Davis Powerhouse Theater (Power Plant), 1965-1972
    - [Plans] Experimental Theater - Proposed Plans, 1965; (4 items) (Map Case - Drawer 60)
    - [Plans] Experimental Theater, 1965, 1968 (Roll Boxes 282-283)
    - [Plans] Miscellaneous Experimental Theater, circa 1965-1967 (Roll Boxes 283-284)
    - [Plans] Architect's drawing of Powerhouse Theatre, circa 1970-1973 (Map Case - Drawer 44)
    - [Plans] [Experimental Theater] "Drama Work Shop", 1972 (Roll Boxes 296-297)
    - [Plans] [Experimental Theater Drama Work Shop], 1972 (Roll Box 299)
    - [Plans] Drama, Flannagan Theater, [1972?] (Roll Box 293)
    - [Plans] Bennington College Science Building [possibly used as model for Experimental Theater lighting?], undated (Roll Box 294)
    - [Plans] Powerhouse Theater, undated (Map Case - Drawer 120)
  - President's House, [1895]
    - [Plans] President's House – Plans, [1895]; (8 items, very poor condition) (Map Case - Drawer 59)
  - Rockefeller Hall, 1896-1989
    - [Plans] Rockefeller Hall, 1896, undated (Roll Box 191)
    - [Plans] Rockefeller Hall, [1896?] (Roll Box 185)
    - [Plans] Rockefeller Hall, 1897 (Roll Box 184)
    - [Plans] Rockefeller Hall, 1940 (Roll Box 182)
    - [Plans] Rockefeller Hall, 1949 (Roll Box 186)
    - [Plans] Rockefeller Hall, 1950, undated (Roll Box 188)
    - [Plans] Rockefeller Hall, 1967, 1987, undated (Roll Box 215)
    - [Plans] Rockefeller Building, 1980 (Roll Box 105)
    - [Plans] Rockefeller Skyline Windows, 1987 (Roll Box 297)
    - [Plans] [Rockefeller?] Skyline Windows, 1987 (Roll Box 314)
    - [Plans] Rockefeller Hall Window Replacement, 1988 (Roll Box 261)
    - [Plans] Rockefeller Hall, Political Sciences Offices, 1989 (Roll Box 274)
    - [Plans] Rockefeller Hall, undated (Map Case - Drawer 122)
    - [Plans] Rockefeller Hall Floor Plans, undated (Roll Box 338)
    - [Plans] Rockefeller Hall Vestibule - ?, undated (Roll Box 191)
  - Sanders Classroom (Sanders Chemistry), 1907-1989
    - [Plans] Chemistry Building, 1907 (Roll Box 334)
    - [Plans] Chemistry Building, 1907, undated (Roll Box 273)
    - [Plans] Sanders Chemistry, 1908 (Roll Box 333)
    - [Plans] Chemistry Building, 1966 (Roll Box 247)
    - [Plans] Chemistry Building, 1966 (Roll Box 268)
    - [Plans] Sanders Sprinklers, 1971 (Roll Box 262)
    - [Plans] Sanders Chemistry Building Safety Rehabilitation Study, 1978 (Roll Box 267)
    - [Plans] Chemistry Building, Dubin Bloone Associates, 1981 (Roll Box 247)
    - [Plans] Sanders Classroom Bldg, 1987 (Roll Box 162)
    - [Plans] Sanders Building, 1987 (Roll Box 214)
    - [Plans] Sanders Classroom Seating Plan, 1989 (Roll Box 326)
    - [Plans] "Chemical Lab Details", undated (Roll Box 266)
    - [Plans] "Chemistry Building", undated (Roll Box 177)
    - [Plans] "Chemistry Building", undated (Roll Box 178)
    - [Plans] "Chemistry Lab Table Details", undated (Roll Box 266)
    - [Plans] "Chemistry Lab Tables Old Tracings", undated (Roll Box 231)
    - [Plans] Chemistry Building, undated (Roll Box 265)
    - [Plans] Chemistry Building, undated (Roll Box 266)
    - [Plans] Sanders Chemistry, undated (Roll Box 265)
    - [Plans] Sanders Chemistry, undated (Roll Box 336)
    - [Plans] Sanders Chemistry Bench Details, undated (Roll Box 266)
    - [Plans] Sanders Classroom, undated (Map Case - Drawer 123)
  - Sanders Physics, [1915]-1930
    - [Plans] Academic Buildings - Proposed Physics and Psychology Building (Folder 3 of 3), [1915], 1930, undated (Map Case - Drawer 60)
    - [Plans] Physics Lab, Ewing and Allen, 1922 (Roll Box 175)
    - [Plans] Sanders Physics Building, 1922 (Roll Box 181)
    - [Plans] Sanders Physics Building Floor Plans, Ewing and Allen, 1922 (Roll Box 182)
    - [Plans] Sanders Physics Framing, 1924 (Roll Box 173)
    - [Plans] Sanders Physics, 1924 (Roll Box 173)
    - [Plans] Physics Lab, Ewing and Allen, 1924 (Roll Box 179)
    - [Plans] Sanders Physics As Built, 1925 (Roll Box 174)
    - [Plans] Sanders Physics Heating and Ventilation, 1925 (Roll Box 174)
    - [Plans] Sanders Physics Revised Framing, 1925 (Roll Box 181)
    - [Plans] Sanders Physics General Plan, circa 1925 (Roll Box 180)
    - [Plans] Academic Buildings - Proposed Physics and Psychology Building (Folder 1 of 3), undated; (3 items) (Map Case - Drawer 58)
    - [Plans] Physics Lab Heating and Ventilation, Ewing and Allen, undated (Roll Box 177)
    - [Plans] Sanders Physics, undated (Map Case - Drawer 123)
    - [Plans] Sanders Physics, undated (Roll Box 176)
    - [Plans] [Sanders Physics], undated (Roll Box 179)
    - [Plans] Sanders Physics Electrical and Plumbing, undated (Roll Box 176)
  - Shiva Theater (Coal Bin Theater), undated
    - [Plans] Shiva Theater (Coal Bin Theater), undated (Map Case - Drawer 124)
  - Skinner Hall of Music, 1930-1991
    - [Plans] Skinner Hall - Allen and Collens, 1930 (Roll Boxes 29-30)
    - [Plans] Skinner Hall - Allen and Collens, 1930 (Roll Box 35)
    - [Plans] Skinner Hall - Allen and Collens, 1930 (Roll Box 39)
    - [Plans] Skinner Hall, 1930 (Roll Box 51)
    - [Plans] Skinner Hall "Electrical Plan", 1930 (Roll Box 52)
    - [Plans] Skinner Hall, 1930 (Roll Boxes 52-54)
    - [Plans] Skinner Hall "Radio Plans", 1930 (Roll Box 55)
    - [Plans] Skinner Hall Metal Bookstacks, 1930 (Roll Box 145)
    - [Plans] Skinner Hall Fourth Floor Plumbing, 1930 (Roll Box 262)
    - [Plans] Skinner Hall, Allen and Collens, framing, 1930 (Roll Box 326)
    - [Plans] Skinner Basement, 1968 (Roll Box 262)
    - [Plans] Skinner Hall, 1991 (Roll Box 29)
    - [Plans] Skinner Hall North Elevation, undated (Roll Box 294)
    - [Plans] Skinner smokestack, undated (Map Case - Drawer 125)
  - Student Housing - General, 1906-1971
    - [Plans] Residence halls, 1906 (Roll Box 348)
    - [Plans] Proposed Dormitories - Multiple Projects - Allen and Collens, Architects (Folder 3 of 3), 1923, undated; (3 items) (Map Case - Drawer 56)
    - [Plans] Specifications for Vassar dormitories, Allen and Collens, 1926 (Roll Box 233)
    - [Plans] Quad, Refectory, 1926 (Roll Box 361)
    - [Plans] Proposed Dormitories - Unidentified Projects - Faulkner, Kingsbury, and Stenhouse, Architects (Folder 1 of 3), 1941, undated; (2 items) (Map Case - Drawer 56)
    - [Plans] Dining Halls - Proposed Plans, 1951, 1960, undated; (6 items) (Map Case - Drawer 56)
    - [Plans] Proposed Josselyn-Jewett Dining Hall, 1966 (Roll Box 241)
    - [Plans] Proposed Josselyn-Jewett Dining Hall - Elevation, 1966 (Roll Box 241)
    - [Plans] Proposed Josselyn-Jewett Dining Hall - Basements of Josselyn and Jewett, 1966 (Roll Box 241)
    - [Plans] Proposed Josselyn-Jewett Dining Hall, 1966 (Roll Box 242)
    - [Plans] Proposed Josselyn-Jewett Dining Hall - Elevation and Landscape Plan, 1966 (Roll Box 242)
    - [Plans] Quad Building Staff Toilets, 1966 (Roll Box 242)
    - [Plans] Proposed Alterations "All Quad Houses", 1966 (Roll Box 243)
    - [Plans] Proposed Josselyn-Jewett Dining Hall, 1966 (Roll Box 244)
    - [Plans] Quad Landscape Plan, 1966 (Roll Box 244)
    - [Plans] Dormitory Dining Hall Plan, 1966 (Roll Box 287)
    - [Plans] Josselyn House and Jewett House, 1966-1967 (Roll Boxes 103-104)
    - [Plans] Josselyn House and Jewett House, 1966-1967 (Roll Box 109)
    - [Plans] Miscellaneous Dormitory Plans, circa 1966-1967 (Roll Box 163)
    - [Plans] Miscellaneous Dormitories, 1967 (Roll Box 215)
    - [Plans] Residences Mechanical and Electrical Plans, Hugh Stubbins and Associates, 1970 (Roll Boxes 245-246)
    - [Plans] Residence Hall Study, Stubbins, 1970 (Roll Boxes 285-286)
    - [Plans] Residence Hall Study, Stubbins, 1970 (Roll Boxes 288-292)
    - [Plans] Vassar College Residences, Stubbins, 1970 (Roll Box 298)
    - [Plans] Miscellaneous Dormitories, 1971 (Roll Box 214)
    - [Plans] "Student Housing", 1971 (Roll Box 297)
    - [Plans] Dining Hall, undated; (1 item) (Map Case - Drawer 46)
    - [Plans] Dining Halls - Proposed Plans for Quad, undated; (1 item) (Map Case - Drawer 46)
    - [Plans] Proposed Josselyn-Jewett Dining Hall - Preliminary plans, undated (Roll Box 108)
    - [Plans] Quad houses, undated (Map Case - Drawer 120)
    - [Plans] Quadrangle plan, undated; (1 item) (Map Case - Drawer 46)
    - [Plans] Residence halls, undated (Roll Box 347)
    - [Plans] Residence halls, undated (Roll Box 359)
    - [Plans] "Residence Hall," Allen and Collens, undated (Roll Box 266)
  - Student Housing - Cushing House, circa 1911-1970
    - [Plans] Cushing House, circa 1911 (Roll Box 230)
    - [Plans] Cushing House, 1926 (Roll Box 224)
    - [Plans] Proposed Dormitories - Cushing House - Allen and Collens, Architects (Folder 2 of 3), 1926, undated; (4 items) (Map Case - Drawer 56)
    - [Plans] Cushing House, 1968 (Roll Box 254)
    - [Plans] Cushing House, 1968, 1970 (Roll Box 216)
    - [Plans] Cushing House, undated (Map Case - Drawer 78)
  - Student Housing - Davison House, 1966-1987
    - [Plans] Strong, Raymond, Davison, Lathrop, 1966 (Roll Box 64)
    - [Plans] Davison House Alteration, 1966 (Roll Box 241)
    - [Plans] Raymond and Davison Houses, 1966 (Roll Box 243)
    - [Plans] Davison House, 1967, 1971, 1987 (Roll Box 252)
    - [Plans] Davison House Floor Plan, 1971 (Roll Box 287)
    - [Plans] Davison House, undated (Map Case - Drawer 79)
    - [Plans] "Davison", undated (Roll Box 65)
    - [Plans] Davison House, undated (Roll Box 254)
    - [Plans] Davison House plans, undated (Roll Box 358)
  - Student Housing - Dexter M. Ferry Jr. Cooperative House (Ferry House), 1949-1950
    - [Plans] Preliminary Plan Area About Cooperative House, drawing and photostat, 1949 Apr; (1 item) (Map Case - Drawer 57)
    - [Plans] [Ferry House] Co-operative Dormitory Poughkeepsie Iron and Metal Company, 1950 (Roll Box 314)
    - [Plans] [Ferry House] Co-operative Dormitory, M.Breuer, 1950 (Roll Boxes 312-313)
    - [Plans] Co-Operative Dormitory, 1950 (Roll Box 259)
    - [Plans] Proposed Services for Co-Operative Dormitory, 1950 (Roll Box 233)
    - [Plans] Ferry House, undated (Map Case - Drawer 86)
  - Student Housing - Jewett House (North Hall), 1966-1973
    - [Plans] Jewett House, 1966 (Roll Box 243)
    - [Plans] Jewett House, 1966 (Roll Box 244)
    - [Plans] Jewett House, 1967 (Roll Box 252)
    - [Plans] Jewett House, 1971 (Roll Box 252)
    - [Plans] Jewett House (revised 1973), 1970, 1973 (Roll Box 254)
    - [Plans] [North Hall?], undated (Roll Box 100)
    - [Plans] Jewett House, undated (Roll Box 110)
    - [Plans] Jewett House, undated (Map Case - Drawer 90)
    - [Plans] Jewett House, undated (Map Case - Drawer 91)
  - Student Housing - Josselyn Hall, 1966/1972
    - [Plans] Josselyn New Window and Floor Construction North Wing, 1966 (Roll Box 241)
    - [Plans] Josselyn Basement, 1966 (Roll Box 241)
    - [Plans] Josselyn House, 1966 (Roll Boxes 243-244)
    - [Plans] Josselyn Basement, 1966 (Roll Box 247)
    - [Plans] Josselyn House, 1972 (Roll Box 104)
    - [Plans] Josselyn Hall, undated (Map Case - Drawer 92)
    - [Plans] Josselyn House, undated (Roll Box 252)
    - [Plans] Josselyn House, undated (Roll Box 255)
  - Student Housing - Lathrop House, circa 1900-1989
    - [Plans] Lathrop House plans, circa 1900 (Roll Box 349)
    - [Plans] Lathrop, 1945 (Roll Box 64)
    - [Plans] Lathrop House, 1962, 1975 (Roll Box 107)
    - [Plans] Strong, Raymond, Davison, Lathrop, 1966 (Roll Box 64)
    - [Plans] Lathrop House Proposed Alterations, 1966 (Roll Box 243)
    - [Plans] Raymond and Lathrop Proposed Alterations, 1966 (Roll Box 244)
    - [Plans] Lathrop House, 1967 (Roll Box 252)
    - [Plans] Lathrop House, 1971 (Roll Box 273)
    - [Plans] Lathrop Hall Alterations, 1975 (Roll Box 241)
    - [Plans] Lathrop, 1988 (Roll Boxes 63-64)
    - [Plans] Lathrop, 1989 (Roll Box 65)
    - [Plans] Lathrop House, undated (Roll Box 254)
    - [Plans] Lathrop House Floor Plan, undated (Roll Box 277)
    - [Plans] Lathrop House plans, undated (Roll Box 360)
    - [Plans] Lathrop House, undated (Map Case - Drawer 98)
  - Student Housing - Emma Hartman Noyes House, 1954-1974
    - [Plans] Noyes Site Plan Study, Eero Saarinen, 1954 (Roll Box 274)
    - [Plans] Noyes, Eero Saarinen, 1957 (Roll Box 274)
    - [Plans] Noyes Site Plan Study, Eero Saarinen, 1957 (Roll Box 275)
    - [Plans] Noyes Preliminary Drawings, Roche and Dinkeloo, 1966 (Roll Box 275)
    - [Plans] Noyes Preliminary Drawings, Roche and Dinkeloo, 1967 (Roll Box 280)
    - [Plans] Noyes House, 1969 (Roll Box 252)
    - [Plans] Noyes House, 1969 (Roll Box 255)
    - [Plans] Noyes Hall Alterations, 1974 (Roll Box 164)
    - [Plans] Noyes Building - Proposed Plans (Folder 1 of 2), undated; (3 items) (Map Case - Drawer 54)
    - [Plans] Noyes Building - Proposed Plans (Folder 2 of 2), undated; (5 items ) (Map Case - Drawer 56)
    - [Plans] Noyes Hall, undated (Map Case - Drawer 115)
    - [Plans] Noyes [Roche and Dinkeloo ?], undated (Roll Box 281)
    - [Plans] Noyes House plans, undated (Roll Box 345)
  - Student Housing - Raymond Hall, 1910-1989
    - [Plans] Raymond House Lighting, Timmis, 1910 (Roll Box 186)
    - [Plans] Raymond House, Allen and Collens, 1926, undated (Roll Box 183)
    - [Plans] Raymond House, circa 1926 (Roll Boxes 191-192)
    - [Plans] Strong, Raymond, Davison, Lathrop, 1966 (Roll Box 64)
    - [Plans] Raymond and Davison Houses, 1966 (Roll Box 243)
    - [Plans] Raymond and Lathrop Proposed Alterations, 1966 (Roll Box 244)
    - [Plans] Raymond House Proposed Alterations, 1966 (Roll Box 248)
    - [Plans] Raymond House, Renovations [not done], 1966 (Roll Box 287)
    - [Plans] Raymond House, 1967, 1971, 1987 (Roll Box 252)
    - [Plans] Raymond House (revised 1973), 1969, 1973 (Roll Box 254)
    - [Plans] Raymond House Electrical Alterations, 1989 (Roll Box 189)
    - [Plans] Raymond House, undated (Roll Box 182)
    - [Plans] Raymond House, Francis R. Allen, undated (Roll Box 187)
    - [Plans] Raymond House Attic Plans, undated (Roll Boxes 189-190)
    - [Plans] Raymond House Attic Plans, Allen and Collens, undated (Roll Box 190)
    - [Plans] Raymond House, undated (Roll Box 335)
    - [Plans] Raymond House, undated (Roll Box 339)
    - [Plans] Raymond House, undated (Roll Box 355)
    - [Plans] Raymond House, undated (Roll Box 356)
    - [Plans] Raymond House, undated (Map Case - Drawer 121)
  - Student Housing - South Commons, undated
    - [Plans] Student Housing - South Commons, undated (Map Case - Drawer 126)
  - Student Housing - Strong House, 1927-1990
    - [Plans] Strong House, 1927 (Roll Box 212)
    - [Plans] Strong, Raymond, Davison, Lathrop, 1966 (Roll Box 64)
    - [Plans] Strong House, 1966 (Roll Box 241)
    - [Plans] Strong House, 1967 (Roll Box 252)
    - [Plans] Strong House, 1969 (Roll Box 210)
    - [Plans] Strong House Electrical Plan, 1990 (Roll Box 207)
    - [Plans] Strong House, undated (Map Case - Drawer 127)
    - [Plans] Strong House, undated (Map Case - Drawer 128)
    - [Plans] Strong, undated (Roll Box 205)
    - [Plans] Strong House, Francis R. Allen, undated (Roll Box 208)
    - [Plans] Strong House Heating Plans, undated (Roll Box 209)
    - [Plans] Strong House, undated (Roll Box 360)
  - Student Housing - Terrace Apartments, 1972
    - [Plans] Terrace Housing, 1972 (Roll Box 214)
    - [Plans] Terrace Apartments plan, 1972; (1 item) (Map Case - Drawer 46)
    - [Plans] Terrace Apartments, undated (Map Case - Drawer 134)
  - Student Housing - Town Houses, undated
    - [Plans] Town Houses, undated (Map Case - Drawer 135)
  - Swift Hall (Infirmary), 1899-1968
    - [Plans] Swift Infirmary - Plans, 1899; (9 items, very poor condition) (Map Case - Drawer 56)